[
  {
    "front": "cent",
    "back": "百"
  },
  {
    "front": "mille",
    "back": "千"
  },
  {
    "front": "dix mille",
    "back": "万"
  },
  {
    "front": "yen",
    "back": "円"
  },
  {
    "front": "avant, plus tôt",
    "back": "先"
  },
  {
    "front": "vivre, naître, produire, nouveau",
    "back": "生"
  },
  {
    "front": "étude",
    "back": "学"
  },
  {
    "front": "école",
    "back": "校"
  },
  {
    "front": "père",
    "back": "父"
  },
  {
    "front": "mère",
    "back": "母"
  }
]
